Jillian FitzMaurice

Extensive experience in UI/UX, product testing, and front-end development gained from working at a small startup. Dedicated to leveraging conceptual and creative thinking to elevate user experiences beyond the ordinary. A firm believer in communication, open-mindedness, and integrity and good design flows like a story.

EXPERIENCE

Legacy Architects, Denver, CO — UI Designer and React Dev

March 2024 - Current (part-time contract)

- Created and collaborated on new feature designs in Figma.
- Developed and updated components in React js.

Software Built by Design, Remote — Front-end Dev and Designer

March 2022 - May 2024

- Orchestrated close collaborations with clients from inception to a final product, translating visions into market-ready products.
- Created full front-end builds in a low-code software.
- Integrated Chat GPT to create an Al tutoring software.
- Promoted after 1 year to lead designer and front-end dev on a major internal project.

The Woods Fine Jewelry, Denver, CO — Product Designer

Feb 2015 - January 2021

 Created new designs while maintaining brand identity while monitored stock and sales of assets to ensure greatest profit returns.

LINKS

Portfolio: https://shyfidelity.github.io/jillian_codes/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jillianfitzmaurice100/

PROJECTS

Boltstack, https://www.boltstack.com/

Lead Designer and Front End Architect, responsible for creating all graphics, animations, and website design.

WonderInk, https://app.wonderink.org/

Username: jillian@softwarebb.com / pw: Church100!

Served as Front-end developer and project lead for a Learning Management System for educators and families.

Edqualis, https://esp-dev.softwarebbd.com/?rr dev=true

Username: test@user.com / pw: Password01

Revamped the entire application with a sleek, modern design, and created consistency. This new design created greater interest from stakeholders.

CONTACT

nenver, CO 80247



303.901.3230



fitzmauricejillian@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Suites
- Artistic eve
- Branding
- Color Theory
- ❖ CRUD
- CSS / CSS Frameworks
- Data sets
- Design
- Figma
- Github
- ♦ lira
- Kanban Boards
- Media Queries
- MS Office
- No-code applications
- Problem solving
- React
- Responsive Design
- Shopify
- Slack
- Tailwind CSS
- Technical Eloquence
- Version Control
- Visual Design
- Visual Hierarchy
- Wireframing

EDUCATION

Denver University

Denver, CO May 2021 - Dec 2021 Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

Milwaukee Institute of Art & Design

Milwaukee, WI May 2007 - Dec 2013

Bachelor of Fine Art / Dean's list

Burren College of Art

Ballyvaughan, Ireland May 2007 - Dec

Bachelor of Fine Art / Study abroad